Register of the Robert Charles Hill papers
Hoover Institution Archives
- Political Years File I, 1959-1969
  - Correspondence, 1960-1966
    - Campbell, Duncan A., III, 1963 (Box-folder 93: 58)
    - Campbell, E. H., 1962 (Box-folder 93: 59)
    - Campbell, Harold J., 1966 (Box-folder 93: 60)
    - Campbell, John L., 1962 (Box-folder 93: 61)
    - Canney, Ethel M., 1961-1966 (Box-folder 93: 62)
    - Capehart, Homer E., 1961 (Box-folder 93: 63)
    - Capik, Theodore S., 1960-1962 (Box-folder 93: 64)
    - Capon, Frank F., 1964 (Box-folder 93: 65)
    - Caredis, Edward A., 1965 (Box-folder 93: 66)
    - Carignan, Norman, 1965-1966 (Box-folder 93: 67)
    - Carlson, Elinore, 1962 (Box-folder 93: 68)
    - Carlson, Frank, 1964-1965 (Box-folder 93: 69)
    - Carlyle Hotel (New York City), 1966 (Box-folder 93: 70)
    - Carmona, Charles C., 1962 (Box-folder 93: 71)
    - Carnes, Louise, 1961 (Box-folder 93: 72)
    - Carpenter, Ralph G., II, 1961 (Box-folder 93: 73)
    - Carr, John, 1961 (Box-folder 93: 74)
    - Carr, Mary E., 1961-1962 (Box-folder 93: 75)
    - Carrillo, Rene, 1965 (Box-folder 93: 76)
    - Carrillo Flores, Antonio, 1961 (Box-folder 93: 77)
    - Carson, Mrs. J. E., 1965 (Box-folder 93: 78)
    - Carter, Ella, 1965 (Box-folder 93: 79)
    - Carter, R. D., 1965 (Box-folder 93: 80)
    - Cartwright, Robert F., 1961-1966 (Box-folder 93: 81)
    - Casariego, Mario, 1961 (Box-folder 93: 82)
    - Casey, John W., 1964-1965 (Box-folder 93: 83)
    - Cassoday, Helga, 1964 (Box-folder 93: 84)
    - Castan, Ernest, 1961 (Box-folder 93: 85)
    - Castro, Raul H., 1966 (Box-folder 93: 86)
    - Castro Beeche, Ricardo, 1961 (Box-folder 93: 87)
    - Catledge, Turner, 1962 (Box-folder 93: 88)
    - Cato, Gillis, Jr., 1961 (Box-folder 93: 89)
    - Cave des Roys, 1963 (Box-folder 93: 90)
    - Cecil, Zack R., 1964 (Box-folder 93: 91)
    - Celler, Emanuel, 1961 (Box-folder 93: 92)
    - Chamberlain, Charles E., 1962 (Box-folder 94: 1)
    - Chamberlain, Edward T., Jr., 1961-1964 (Box-folder 94: 2)
    - Chamberlin, Lyman W., 1961-1965 (Box-folder 94: 3)
    - Chamberlin, Marguerite, 1965-1966 (Box-folder 94: 4)
    - Champion, George, 1965 (Box-folder 94: 5)
    - Chandler, James E., 1966 (Box-folder 94: 6)
    - Chandler, Melvin H., 1961-1963 (Box-folder 94: 7)
    - Chaney, Verne, 1966 (Box-folder 94: 8)
    - Chase, A. Richard, 1961 (Box-folder 94: 9)
    - Chatterbox Club, 1962 (Box-folder 94: 10)
    - Chavez Peon, Enrique, 1962 (Box-folder 94: 11)
    - Chenet, A. J., 1961-1962 (Box-folder 94: 12)
    - Chinese News Service, 1966 (Box-folder 94: 13)
    - Chivers, Howard P., 1961 (Box-folder 94: 14)
    - Chotiner, Murray M., 1964 (Box-folder 94: 15)
    - Church, Charles T., II, 1966 (Box-folder 94: 16)
    - Church, Marguerite Stitt, 1961-1962 (Box-folder 94: 17)
    - Cibula, Frank G., 1965 (Box-folder 94: 18)
    - Citizens for Shanley, 1964 (Box-folder 94: 19)
    - Claflin, William H., 1964 (Box-folder 94: 20)
    - Clark, Charles Patrick, 1965-1966 (Box-folder 94: 21)
    - Clark, Fred G., 1964 (Box-folder 94: 22)
    - Clark, George R., 1963 (Box-folder 94: 23)
    - Clark, Helen, 1963 (Box-folder 94: 24)
    - Clark, Howard L., 1961 (Box-folder 94: 25)
    - Clark, Shirley M., 1961 (Box-folder 94: 26)
    - Clark, William, 1966 (Box-folder 94: 27)
    - Clarkson, Stuart R., 1961 (Box-folder 94: 28)
    - Claxton, Philander P., Jr., 1962 (Box-folder 94: 29)
    - Clement, William E., 1961 (Box-folder 94: 30)
    - Cleveland, James C., 1962-1966 (Box-folder 94: 31)
    - Clough, Barry L., 1964-1965 (Box-folder 94: 32)
    - Clough, Clinton, undated (Box-folder 94: 33)
    - Coates, F. M., 1964 (Box-folder 94: 34)
    - Cobb, Edward S., 1962 (Box-folder 94: 35)
    - Cochran, Dwight M., 1965 (Box-folder 94: 36)
    - Cody, Gwen, 1962 (Box-folder 94: 37)
    - Coe, Douglas E., 1962-1963 (Box-folder 94: 38)
    - Coffin, Edith G., 1961 (Box-folder 94: 39)
    - Colby, John H., 1961-1966 (Box-folder 94: 40)
    - Colby, Pamela, 1965 (Box-folder 94: 41)
    - Colby, Ralph, 1963 (Box-folder 94: 42)
    - Colby, Raymond E., 1964 (Box-folder 94: 43)
    - Colby, Reginald M., 1964 (Box-folder 94: 44)
    - Cole, Douglas Seaman, 1961-1962 (Box-folder 94: 45)
    - Cole, Stacey W., 1962-1966 (Box-folder 94: 46)
    - Collins, Barney, 1961 (Box-folder 94: 47)
    - Collyer, Rita, 1961 (Box-folder 94: 48)
    - Colt, John B., 1961-1962 (Box-folder 94: 49)
    - Committee for Economic Development, 1963 (Box-folder 94: 50)
    - Connally, John B., 1966 (Box-folder 94: 51)
    - Connecticut Valley Airways, 1961 (Box-folder 94: 52)
    - Connor, John T., 1965 (Box-folder 94: 53)
    - Connors, Philip, 1960-1961 (Box-folder 94: 54)
    - Conrad, Margaret M., 1961-1965 (Box-folder 94: 55)
    - Consejo Nacional de Turismo (Mexico), 1964 (Box-folder 94: 56)
    - Cook, Raymond A., 1966 (Box-folder 94: 57)
    - Cooke, Ray F., 1961 (Box-folder 94: 58)
    - Cooper, Bradley M., 1962 (Box-folder 94: 59)
    - Copp, Charles W., 1966 (Box-folder 94: 60)
    - Corcoran, Howard F., 1961-1964 (Box-folder 94: 61)
    - Corcoran, Thomas G., 1961-1966 (Box-folder 94: 62)
    - Correa M., Jose de Jesus, 1964 (Box-folder 94: 63)
    - Corso, Philip J., 1960-1963 (Box-folder 94: 64)
    - Cotton, Norris, 1961-1966 (Box-folder 94: 65)
    - Cottrell, David, Jr., 1961 (Box-folder 94: 66)
    - Couchois, Garrett J., 1961 (Box-folder 94: 67)
    - Council for Latin America, 1965-1966 (Box-folder 94: 68)
    - Courtney, Kent, 1961 (Box-folder 94: 69)
    - Couturier, Jean J., 1964-1965 (Box-folder 94: 70)
    - Covey, Thomas R., Jr., 1966 (Box-folder 94: 71)
    - Coyle, Alfred J., 1962 (Box-folder 94: 72)
    - Crafts, Prescott C., Jr., 1966 (Box-folder 94: 73)
    - Cramer, William C., 1964 (Box-folder 94: 74)
    - Cranmer, Forrest, 1963 (Box-folder 94: 75)
    - Craw, Richard, 1966 (Box-folder 94: 76)
    - Creiger, H. L., 1966 (Box-folder 94: 77)
    - Crockett, Kennedy M., 1961 (Box-folder 94: 78)
    - Crook, Clark Harris, 1961 (Box-folder 94: 79)
    - Crook, Frank M., undated (Box-folder 94: 80)
    - Crosby, H. Ashton, 1966 (Box-folder 94: 81)
    - Crowe, Philip Kingsland, 1964-1966 (Box-folder 94: 82)
    - Cruikshank, Paul, 1962-1963 (Box-folder 94: 83)
    - Cruz, Hector, 1961 (Box-folder 94: 84)
    - Cuellar, Alfredo B., 1961-1962 (Box-folder 95: 1)
    - Culbertson, William S., 1961 (Box-folder 95: 2)
    - Cullen, Edward H., 1961-1965 (Box-folder 95: 3)
    - Cummings, Leslie S., 1963 (Box-folder 95: 4)
    - Cure, Mortimer D., 1962-1966 (Box-folder 95: 5)
    - Curran, Kenneth E., 1961 (Box-folder 95: 6)
    - Curtis, John J., 1961 (Box-folder 95: 7)
    - Cusanelli, Erna A., 1962 (Box-folder 95: 8)
    - Cushman, Robert, 1961 (Box-folder 95: 9)
    - Cuthbert, George, 1962 (Box-folder 95: 10)
    - Cutler, Robert, 1961-1963 (Box-folder 95: 11)
    - Dagand, Henry H., 1962 (Box-folder 95: 12)
    - Daly, Kenneth H., 1962 (Box-folder 95: 13)
    - Dance, Edward T., 1962 (Box-folder 95: 14)
    - Danciger, Jack, 1961-1962 (Box-folder 95: 15)
    - Darling, Charles M., 1961 (Box-folder 95: 16)
    - Darling, Philip M., 1961 (Box-folder 95: 17)
    - Dartmouth College, 1960-1964 (Box-folder 95: 18)
    - Dauphinot, Clarence, Jr., 1964-1966 (Box-folder 95: 19)
    - Davis, A. D., 1966 (Box-folder 95: 20)
    - Deacon, W. A., 1964 (Box-folder 95: 21)
    - Dean, David M., 1965 (Box-folder 95: 22)
    - Dean, Sterling, 1961 (Box-folder 95: 23)
    - Degler, Carroll M., 1961 (Box-folder 95: 24)
    - De la Garza, Eligio, 1961 (Box-folder 95: 25)
    - Delaney, Robert F., 1962 (Box-folder 95: 26)
    - De Lima, David, 1962-1966 (Box-folder 95: 27)
    - Delman Shoe Salon, 1964 (Box-folder 95: 28)
    - De Macaya, Margarita, 1966 (Box-folder 95: 29)
    - Demetrakopoulas, Cheryl, 1961 (Box-folder 95: 30)
    - DeMott, Clayton M., Jr., 1962-1966 (Box-folder 95: 31)
    - DeMott, John H., 1962 (Box-folder 95: 32)
    - DeMott, Thomas B., 1961-1966 (Box-folder 95: 33)
    - Dercole, Donald, 1966 (Box-folder 95: 34)
    - Desmond, John F., 1961-1965 (Box-folder 95: 35)
    - De Toledano, Ralph, 1963 (Box-folder 95: 36)
    - Devin-Adair Company, 1964 (Box-folder 95: 37)
    - De Voursney, Robert, 1961 (Box-folder 95: 38)
    - Dewey, Thomas E., 1965 (Box-folder 95: 39)
    - De Wilmot, Martha P., 1963 (Box-folder 95: 40)
    - Dexter, Ruth, 1962 (Box-folder 95: 41)
    - Diamond, Luna, 1962-1963 (Box-folder 95: 42)
    - Diaz, Jose Gregorio, 1964-1966 (Box-folder 95: 43)
    - Dichter, David, 1966 (Box-folder 95: 44)
    - Dickey, John S., 1962 (Box-folder 95: 45)
    - Diggle, Arthur V., 1961-1966 (Box-folder 95: 46)
    - Di Giorgio, J. S., 1965 (Box-folder 95: 47)
    - Dillon, C. Douglas, 1961 (Box-folder 95: 48)
    - Directory of Directors, 1965 (Box-folder 95: 49)
    - Dirksen, Everett McKinley, 1965-1966 (Box-folder 95: 50)
    - Dix, George C., 1961 (Box-folder 95: 51)
    - Dixon, W. Palmer, 1960 (Box-folder 95: 52)
    - Dodd, Marianne B., 1963 (Box-folder 95: 53)
    - Dodd, Thomas J., 1962-1966 (Box-folder 95: 54)
    - Dodge, John B., 1962-1964 (Box-folder 95: 55)
    - Dodge, John E., 1961 (Box-folder 95: 56)
    - Doerflinger, O. M., 1964 (Box-folder 95: 57)
    - Dole, Joyce, 1962 (Box-folder 95: 58)
    - Donavin, K. H., 1961 (Box-folder 95: 59)
    - Donohoe, Carter H., 1963 (Box-folder 95: 60)
    - Donohue, Timothy, 1961 (Box-folder 95: 61)
    - Dorsey, James, 1965 (Box-folder 96: 1)
    - Dougherty, Harry L., 1961 (Box-folder 96: 2)
    - Dow, Joy, 1961-1964 (Box-folder 96: 3)
    - Downing, Jay, 1961 (Box-folder 96: 4)
    - Drake, Arthur, 1961 (Box-folder 96: 5)
    - Draper, William, 1965 (Box-folder 96: 6)
    - Drayer, Dolores, 1965 (Box-folder 96: 7)
    - Dreier, William, 1961 (Box-folder 96: 8)
    - Dresser, Paula J., 1962 (Box-folder 96: 9)
    - Drew, Robert B., 1961 (Box-folder 96: 10)
    - Drohojowska, Natalia, 1961 (Box-folder 96: 11)
    - Drown, Douglas N., 1961 (Box-folder 96: 12)
    - Drowne, George P., Jr., 1965 (Box-folder 96: 13)
    - Dryfoos, Orvil, 1961-1962 (Box-folder 96: 14)
    - Dubois, Jules, 1963-1966 (Box-folder 96: 15)
    - Du Bouchet, Andres J., Jr., 1960-1966 (Box-folder 96: 16)
    - Duenas, Clairmont, 1965 (Box-folder 96: 17)
    - Duenas, Miguel, 1961-1965 (Box-folder 96: 18)
    - Duke, Angier Biddle, 1961 (Box-folder 96: 19)
    - Dulles, Allen W., 1961-1965 (Box-folder 96: 20)
    - Dulles, Eleanor Lansing, 1962-1964 (Box-folder 96: 21)
    - Dulles, Janet, 1961 (Box-folder 96: 22)
    - Dulles, John W. F., 1962 (Box-folder 96: 23)
    - Duncan, John, 1962 (Box-folder 96: 24)
    - Dunfey Realtors, 1961-1963 (Box-folder 96: 25)
    - Dunn, Margaret, 1961 (Box-folder 96: 26)
    - Duran, Ireneo, 1961 (Box-folder 96: 27)
    - Duranty, Joseph, 1964 (Box-folder 96: 28)
    - Du Vivier, Mrs. Paul, 1964 (Box-folder 96: 29)
    - Dwinell, Lane, 1964 (Box-folder 96: 30)
    - Dworshak, George, 1962 (Box-folder 96: 31)
    - Dyer, Daniel L., 1962-1964 (Box-folder 96: 32)
    - Eager, Auville, 1963-1964 (Box-folder 96: 33)
    - Eager, Dottie, 1966 (Box-folder 96: 34)
    - Eager, Robert C., 1962-1966 (Box-folder 96: 35)
    - Easter Seal Agency of New Hampshire, 1961 (Box-folder 96: 36)
    - Eastland, James O., 1961 (Box-folder 96: 37)
    - Eastman, Scott F., 1961-1964 (Box-folder 96: 38)
    - Eaton, Charles C., 1961 (Box-folder 96: 39)
    - Echols, Percy L., 1961 (Box-folder 96: 40)
    - Eddy, Richard W., 1961 (Box-folder 96: 41)
    - Edison, Charles, 1961 (Box-folder 96: 42)
    - Edwards, John, 1966 (Box-folder 96: 43)
    - Edwards, Max Nixon, 1961 (Box-folder 96: 44)
    - Egger, George E., 1961 (Box-folder 96: 45)
    - Egiz Ordonez, Mauricio, 1964 (Box-folder 96: 46)
    - Ehrmann, Mrs. Henry, 1965 (Box-folder 96: 47)
    - Eichelberger, A. Martin, Jr., 1964-1965 (Box-folder 96: 48)
    - Eisenhower, Dwight D., 1961-1964 (Box-folder 96: 49)
    - Eisenhower, Milton S., 1965 (Box-folder 96: 50)
    - Eleta A., Fernando, 1964-1965 (Box-folder 96: 51)
    - Ellender, Allen J., 1960-1961 (Box-folder 96: 52)
    - Eller, E. M., 1962 (Box-folder 96: 53)
    - Eller, Joseph J., 1962 (Box-folder 96: 54)
    - Elston, Eva M., 1964 (Box-folder 96: 55)
    - Elvove, Joseph T., 1962-1964 (Box-folder 96: 56)
    - Emekle, Dolores Hicabi, 1963 (Box-folder 96: 57)
    - Emery, Ronald, 1962 (Box-folder 96: 58)
    - English, Robert, 1961 (Box-folder 96: 59)
    - Epstean, Catherine M., 1962 (Box-folder 96: 60)
    - Escancona, Frank, 1961 (Box-folder 96: 61)
    - Esquivel, Alberto, 1963 (Box-folder 96: 62)
    - Esquivel, Mario A., 1961-1966 (Box-folder 96: 63)
    - Eurit, Charles E., 1961 (Box-folder 96: 64)
    - Evans, Rowland, 1963-1964 (Box-folder 96: 65)
    - Evans, Thomas W., 1966 (Box-folder 96: 66)
    - Evans, Wayne L., 1965 (Box-folder 96: 67)
    - Everett, James R., 1961 (Box-folder 96: 68)
    - Exchange Students, 1963 (Box-folder 96: 69)
    - Facio, Antonio, 1962 (Box-folder 96: 70)
    - Farland, Joseph S., 1965 (Box-folder 96: 71)
    - Farley, James A., 1961-1966 (Box-folder 96: 72)
    - Farnum, Paul E., 1962-1963 (Box-folder 96: 73)
    - Fauver, Alfred N., 1965 (Box-folder 96: 74)
    - Fay School, 1963 (Box-folder 96: 75)
    - Fellers, Bonner, 1963 (Box-folder 96: 76)
    - Fellows, H. H., Jr., 1961-1963 (Box-folder 96: 77)
    - Fendell, J. D., 1961 (Box-folder 96: 78)
    - Feng, Chih Tsing, 1963 (Box-folder 96: 79)
    - Feng, Edith, 1965 (Box-folder 96: 80)
    - Fernandez, Leo, 1963-1966 (Box-folder 96: 81)
    - Fernandez Rionda, J., 1962 (Box-folder 96: 82)
    - Figueres, Jose, 1961 (Box-folder 96: 83)
    - Figueroa, Gilberto, 1962 (Box-folder 96: 84)
    - Financial Executives Institute, 1966 (Box-folder 96: 85)
    - Finch, Robert H., 1965 (Box-folder 96: 86)
    - Findley, Paul, 1966 (Box-folder 96: 87)
    - Finn, Barbara B., 1964-1965 (Box-folder 96: 88)
    - Finn, John J., 1961-1966 (Box-folder 96: 89)
    - Finnegan, James J., 1962 (Box-folder 96: 90)
    - Finucane, Charles C., 1962 (Box-folder 96: 91)
    - Fisher, John B., 1962 (Box-folder 97: 1)
    - FitzGerald, William H. G., 1964 (Box-folder 97: 2)
    - Flanders, Ralph E., 1961-1963 (Box-folder 97: 3)
    - Fletcher, Margaret, 1961 (Box-folder 97: 4)
    - Fletcher Breton, Enrique, 1963 (Box-folder 97: 5)
    - Fletcher School of Law and Diplomacy, 1963-1965 (Box-folder 97: 6)
    - Flores, Thomas J., Jr., 1961 (Box-folder 97: 7)
    - Flues, A. Gilmore, 1966 (Box-folder 97: 8)
    - Flynn, Fred J., 1965 (Box-folder 97: 9)
    - Foley, Edward H., 1963 (Box-folder 97: 10)
    - Ford, Gerald R., 1965 (Box-folder 97: 11)
    - Ford, John W., 1961-1966 (Box-folder 97: 12)
    - Ford, Joseph P., 1966 (Box-folder 97: 13)
    - Ford Motor Company, 1965 (Box-folder 97: 14)
    - Foreign Policy Research Institute, 1962 (Box-folder 97: 15)
    - Forsten, Weikko, 1961-1966 (Box-folder 97: 16)
    - Fortinberry, Lane, 1965-1966 (Box-folder 97: 17)
    - Foss, Eugene N., II, 1964 (Box-folder 97: 18)
    - Foss, Mary Win, 1963 (Box-folder 97: 19)
    - Fossas Requena, Pedro, 1961 (Box-folder 97: 20)
    - Fothergill, William R., 1964 (Box-folder 97: 21)
    - Fowler, Dan, 1961 (Box-folder 97: 22)
    - Framingham Motor Inn (Framingham, Mass.), 1961 (Box-folder 97: 23)
    - Franco, Natalia, 1963 (Box-folder 97: 24)
    - Franconia College, 1963-1965 (Box-folder 97: 25)
    - Franke, William, 1964-1966 (Box-folder 97: 26)
    - Franklin Management Corporation, 1964 (Box-folder 97: 27)
    - Franz, M. H., 1960-1961 (Box-folder 97: 28)
    - Frawley, Patrick J., Jr., 1965 (Box-folder 97: 29)
    - Freedom Studeies Center, 1966 (Box-folder 97: 30)
    - French, James H., 1961 (Box-folder 97: 31)
    - Freund, Dallas, 1964-1966 (Box-folder 97: 32)
    - Friedman, Benny, 1965 (Box-folder 97: 33)
    - Fulbright, J. W., 1963 (Box-folder 97: 34)
    - Fulks, Hilburne, 1961 (Box-folder 97: 35)
    - Funston, Keith, 1965 (Box-folder 97: 36)
    - Gabbert, Howard M., 1961-1966 (Box-folder 97: 37)
    - Gahagan, Andrew, 1964-1965 (Box-folder 97: 38)
    - Gallagher, John, 1963 (Box-folder 97: 39)
    - Galvin, John T., 1964 (Box-folder 97: 40)
    - Gammons, Earl H., 1962-1966 (Box-folder 97: 41)
    - Gammons, Holly, 1964 (Box-folder 97: 42)
    - Gannett, Dorothy F., 1961 (Box-folder 97: 43)
    - Garcia, Mrs. E. G., 1962 (Box-folder 97: 44)
    - Gardner, George P., Jr., 1963-1966 (Box-folder 97: 45)
    - Gardner, Laurence F., 1961 (Box-folder 97: 46)
    - Gardner, Ledyard D., 1962-1965 (Box-folder 97: 47)
    - Garduno, Mrs. Gerald, 1961 (Box-folder 97: 48)
    - Garland, Charles S., 1964 (Box-folder 97: 49)
    - Garrett, Glenn E., 1961 (Box-folder 97: 50)
    - Garrett, Harrison, 1965 (Box-folder 97: 51)
    - Gatchell, Nathan Bangs, II, 1963 (Box-folder 97: 52)
    - Gavaldon, Eugenia, 1961 (Box-folder 97: 53)
    - Geisel, Joseph H., 1962-1964 (Box-folder 97: 54)
    - Georgopoulos Jewelry Store, 1964 (Box-folder 97: 55)
    - Gerber, Thomas W., 1961-1962 (Box-folder 97: 56)
    - Geren, Paul F., 1963 (Box-folder 97: 57)
    - Gibson, Carlos, 1962-1966 (Box-folder 97: 58)
    - Gibson, Raleigh A., 1963-1965 (Box-folder 97: 59)
    - Gilbrede, Rosemary, 1966 (Box-folder 97: 60)
    - Giles, John A., 1961 (Box-folder 97: 61)
    - Gilman, George T., 1965 (Box-folder 97: 62)
    - Gilmer, Ben Screws, 1966 (Box-folder 97: 63)
    - Gilmore, Ken, 1965 (Box-folder 97: 64)
    - Giron, Jose, 1965 (Box-folder 97: 65)
    - Glawe, Benoid E., 1961 (Box-folder 97: 66)
    - Goen, Sargent, 1962-1966 (Box-folder 97: 67)
    - Goheen, Robert F., 1964 (Box-folder 97: 68)
    - Gold, Jeanne, 1961-1965 (Box-folder 97: 69)
    - Goldberg, Arthur J., 1965 (Box-folder 97: 70)
    - Goldberg, Emanuel, 1966 (Box-folder 97: 71)
    - Goldwater, Barry, 1962-1964 (Box-folder 97: 72)
    - Gonzales, Benny, 1961 (Box-folder 97: 73)
    - Goode, Paul K., 1962 (Box-folder 97: 74)
    - Goodrich, Burnell N., 1960-1966 (Box-folder 97: 75)
    - Goodrich, Emmette K., Jr., 1960-1966 (Box-folder 97: 76)
    - Goodwin, Richard, 1961 (Box-folder 97: 77)
    - Gordon, Albert H., 1965 (Box-folder 97: 78)
    - Goss, Walter A., 1962 (Box-folder 97: 79)
    - Gotham Hotel (New York City), 1966 (Box-folder 98: 1)
    - Gott, Philip P., 1962 (Box-folder 98: 2)
    - Gow, Ralph F., 1961 (Box-folder 98: 3)
    - Gowran, Clay, 1961 (Box-folder 98: 4)
    - Grace, J. Peter, 1962-1965 (Box-folder 98: 5)
    - Graham, Billy, 1964 (Box-folder 98: 6)
    - Graham, Earle, 1961 (Box-folder 98: 7)
    - Grand, Gordon, 1963 (Box-folder 98: 8)
    - Grant, Alan G., Jr., 1964 (Box-folder 98: 9)
    - Grant, Catherine, 1964 (Box-folder 98: 10)
    - Gray, Cecil W., 1961-1964 (Box-folder 98: 11)
    - Gray, David, 1961 (Box-folder 98: 12)
    - Gray, Phyllis D. S., 1963 (Box-folder 98: 13)
    - Gray, Robert K., 1961 (Box-folder 98: 14)
    - Green, Wilbur, 1962 (Box-folder 98: 15)
    - Greene, F. J., 1961 (Box-folder 98: 16)
    - Greene, Frank T., 1961 (Box-folder 98: 17)
    - Gregg, David A., 1965 (Box-folder 98: 18)
    - Gregg, Hugh, 1961 (Box-folder 98: 19)
    - Griffith, B. Barret, 1961 (Box-folder 98: 20)
    - Griffiths, Creighton, 1963 (Box-folder 98: 21)
    - Grimes, Frank J., 1961-1962 (Box-folder 98: 22)
    - Griswold, H. B., 1962 (Box-folder 98: 23)
    - Grosberg, Stephen M., 1966 (Box-folder 98: 24)
    - Gruenther, Homer H., 1964-1966 (Box-folder 98: 25)
    - Gruner, Robert H., 1961 (Box-folder 98: 26)
    - Guest, Robert H., 1961 (Box-folder 98: 27)
    - Guider, John W., 1962-1963 (Box-folder 98: 28)
    - Guizar, Tito, 1963 (Box-folder 98: 29)
    - Gullette, Wilmer, 1961-1963 (Box-folder 98: 30)
    - Gullion, Edmund A., 1965-1966 (Box-folder 98: 31)
    - Gunther, W. H., Jr., 1961 (Box-folder 98: 32)
    - Guptill, Charles H., 1961-1965 (Box-folder 98: 33)
    - Gutierrez G., Jaime, 1963 (Box-folder 98: 34)
    - Guyer, Joyce, 1961 (Box-folder 98: 35)
    - Gwynn, Ernest L., 1966 (Box-folder 98: 36)
    - Hasse, Paul, 1966 (Box-folder 98: 37)
    - Habberton, John H., 1962 (Box-folder 98: 38)
    - Hackney, G. Edgar, 1961-1965 (Box-folder 98: 39)
    - Hagerman, Donald C., 1961-1962 (Box-folder 98: 40)
    - Hagerty, James C., 1961-1962 (Box-folder 98: 41)
    - Hague, Fred Joe, 1961 (Box-folder 98: 42)
    - Hall, Leonard, 1964 (Box-folder 98: 43)
    - Hall, Richard L., 1962 (Box-folder 98: 44)
    - Halsted, Isabella, 1961 (Box-folder 98: 45)
    - Halverson, Richard C., 1963-1964 (Box-folder 98: 46)
    - Hamel, Guy, 1961 (Box-folder 98: 47)
    - Hamilton, George T., 1964 (Box-folder 98: 48)
    - Hamilton, John D. M., 1962 (Box-folder 98: 49)
    - Hammacher Schlemmer Company, 1966 (Box-folder 98: 50)
    - Hammer, John L., Jr., 1964 (Box-folder 98: 51)
    - Hampson, Arthur, 1961 (Box-folder 98: 52)
    - Hampson, Harold, 1962 (Box-folder 98: 53)
    - Hampton (N. H.) Union, 1964 (Box-folder 98: 54)
    - Hancock, Mary Louise, 1962 (Box-folder 98: 55)
    - Hancock, Robert A., 1961-1964 (Box-folder 98: 56)
    - Hancock, Stuart, 1961 (Box-folder 98: 57)
    - Hand, Frank, 1962 (Box-folder 98: 58)
    - Hanes, John W., Jr., 1961-1962 (Box-folder 98: 59)
    - Hannah, John W., 1966 (Box-folder 98: 60)
    - Hanson, Simon G., 1965 (Box-folder 98: 61)
    - Hare, Raymond A., 1962 (Box-folder 98: 62)
    - Harlow, Bryce N., 1962-1966 (Box-folder 98: 63)
    - Harper's Magazine, 1960 (Box-folder 98: 64)
    - Harr, Karl G., Jr., 1961 (Box-folder 98: 65)
    - Harrigan, Anthony, 1961 (Box-folder 98: 66)
    - Harris, Janet, 1961 (Box-folder 98: 67)
    - Harris, John B., 1961-1963 (Box-folder 98: 68)
    - Harris, Richard C., 1961 (Box-folder 98: 69)
    - Harrison, Dorothea Katharine, 1966 (Box-folder 98: 70)
    - Harrscom, Ethel L., 1964 (Box-folder 98: 71)
    - Harvey, Lester S., 1963 (Box-folder 98: 72)
    - Harwood, Herbert H., 1963 (Box-folder 98: 73)
    - Hatch, Fletcher A., Jr., 1966 (Box-folder 98: 74)
    - Hatmaker, George E., 1966 (Box-folder 98: 75)
    - Haubrich, W. R., 1962 (Box-folder 98: 76)
    - Hauge, Gabriel, 1961 (Box-folder 98: 77)
    - Hayden, Bruce P., 1962 (Box-folder 98: 78)
    - Hayden, Carl, 1966 (Box-folder 98: 79)
    - Hayden, Helen W., 1964 (Box-folder 98: 80)
    - Hayes, Julian L., 1963 (Box-folder 98: 81)
    - Hays, Brooks, 1961 (Box-folder 98: 82)
    - Healey, Frances, 1962 (Box-folder 98: 83)
    - Heath, Harrison M., 1961 (Box-folder 98: 84)
    - Heckelmann, Charles N., 1964 (Box-folder 98: 85)
    - Hector, Louis J., 1965 (Box-folder 98: 86)
    - Hedges, Jim, undated (Box-folder 98: 87)
    - Hedlund, Anita R., 1961 (Box-folder 98: 88)
    - Heimark, Jacob Vincent, 1960-1966 (Box-folder 98: 89)
    - Heinz, Henry J., II, 1964 (Box-folder 98: 90)
    - Hellyer, Clement David, 1961-1964 (Box-folder 99: 1)
    - Helms, Sherwin P., 1963 (Box-folder 99: 2)
    - Henderson, Donald H., 1966 (Box-folder 99: 3)
    - Henderson, Ernest, 1961 (Box-folder 99: 4)
    - Henkle, James, 1962 (Box-folder 99: 5)
    - Henle, Ray, 1962 (Box-folder 99: 6)
    - Heritage Furniture Company, 1964 (Box-folder 99: 7)
    - Hermand, Marcel J., 1964 (Box-folder 99: 8)
    - Hernandez, J. Roberto, 1961 (Box-folder 99: 9)
    - Herrick, Elinore Morehouse, 1962 (Box-folder 99: 10)
    - Herschel, C. Andrew, 1962 (Box-folder 99: 11)
    - Hesslein, Joanne, 1963 (Box-folder 99: 12)
    - Hesslein, Richard A., 1965 (Box-folder 99: 13)
    - Hibbs, Ben, 1961-1962 (Box-folder 99: 14)
    - Hickernell, James H., 1961 (Box-folder 99: 15)
    - Hickey, Edward J., 1961 (Box-folder 99: 16)
    - Hickey, Frank E., 1965 (Box-folder 99: 17)
    - Hickey, William M., 1962-1966 (Box-folder 99: 18-19)
    - Hicks, C. D., 1962 (Box-folder 99: 20)
    - Hicks, Orton H., 1961-1966 (Box-folder 99: 21)
    - Hiestand, Edgar W., 1961 (Box-folder 99: 22)
    - Higgins, Marguerite, 1961 (Box-folder 99: 23)
    - Hill, Allen, 1962-1966 (Box-folder 99: 24)
    - Hill, Bartlett, 1960 (Box-folder 99: 25)